<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>thomasjbrailey</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on thomasjbrailey</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello!
My name is Thomas and I am a fourth year Political Science: Data Analytics major at UC San Diego.
I am also a research assistant at the Center for the Study of African Political Economy and a lab assistant the Center for Peace and Security Studies.
I am interested in political institutions, elections, secession, and conflict in developing democracies, with a particular focus in sub-Saharan Africa.
My CV can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calculating Electoral Proximity in R</title>
      <link>/post/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/test/</guid>
      <description>What is Electoral Proximity?Electoral proximity is the measure of fractionalization between a presidential and legislative election. That is, how temporally separated a state’s legislative and presidential elections might be. If presidential and legislative elections occur on the same day, they are considered to be proximally maximal. If there is a considerable gap between elections, then there is considered to be less proximity between elections. Gary Cox termed this phrase in Making Votes Count (1997) and builds off of the work of Matthew Shugart, John Carey, Rein Taagepera, and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calculating Electoral Proximity in R</title>
      <link>/posts/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/test/</guid>
      <description>What is Electoral Proximity?Electoral proximity is the measure of fractionalization between a presidential and legislative election. That is, how temporally separated a state’s legislative and presidential elections might be. If presidential and legislative elections occur on the same day, they are considered to be proximally maximal. If there is a considerable gap between elections, then there is considered to be less proximity between elections. Gary Cox termed this phrase in Making Votes Count (1997) and builds off of the work of Matthew Shugart, John Carey, Rein Taagepera, and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for reaching out! Whether it be to talk about politics, music, or just to say &amp;ldquo;hi&amp;rdquo;, it would be great to get to know you!
You can reach me at:
tbrailey@ucsd.edu
thomasjbrailey@gmail.com
+1 (858) 610-2437
Or feel free to follow me on GitHub, LinkedIn, or Twitter (links on my homepage).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Here is a list of my projects and works in progress. Feel free to give them a read through and leave comments/suggestions!
Finished Papers Provisions of Power-Sharing: Assessing the Impacts of Segmental Autonomy
Paper
Replication Package
After Segmental Autonomy: Assessing Conflict and Service Proliferation in Mali&amp;rsquo;s Autonomous Region
Paper
Replication Package
Predicting Rogue State Missile Launches
Paper
Replicaiton Package
Works in Progress Datasets Provisions of Power-Sharing
.xlsx
.csv
.sav
Miscellaneous </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>