<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on thomasjbrailey</title>
    <link>/tags/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on thomasjbrailey</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Brief Note on Replication in R</title>
      <link>/posts/replicability/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/replicability/</guid>
      <description>Replication studies – repeating an existing study/experiment/analysis to see if the results hold up – in the social sciences are essential for the advancement of scientific understanding. See this Vox article for a primer.
On a smaller scale, labs often get their researchers to run what are known as “code audits”. If one researcher is working on an analysis, they hand it over to another researcher for them to run and see if the results are replicable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ridiculously Niche Plots Episode I: Scaled and Faceted Radar Plots</title>
      <link>/posts/niche_plots_i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/niche_plots_i/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to the first episode in a series I like to call “Ridiculously Niche Plots”! An intermittent series where I give a brief rundown of especially strange plots that I have spent hours trying to crack, in the hope that someone, somewhere, struggling to understand the ins and outs of gridExtra or who are hitting their head against a wall because ggplot2 is throwing out a horrifically labyrinthine error, might stumble on this article and have all of their questions answered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electoral Violence in Papua New Guinea </title>
      <link>/posts/png_violence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/png_violence/</guid>
      <description>For the past few months, I have been working as a research assistant for Professors Gareth Nellis and Jasper Cooper. The project focuses on Papua New Guinea’s shift from first-past-the-post to the alternative vote in 2007. One outcome measure we are interested in is electoral-related violence, and whether incidents of violence increased or decreased following the implementation of the alternative vote.
Data on violence in PNG is sparse, and so I was tasked with creating a dataset of all election-related violent incidents around the 2002 and 2007 election periods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calculating Electoral Proximity in R</title>
      <link>/posts/cox_proximity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/cox_proximity/</guid>
      <description>What is Electoral Proximity?Electoral proximity is the measure of fractionalization between a presidential and legislative election. That is, how temporally separated a state’s legislative and presidential elections might be. If presidential and legislative elections occur on the same day, they are considered to be proximally maximal. If there is a considerable gap between elections, then there is considered to be less proximity between elections. Gary Cox termed this phrase in Making Votes Count (1997) and builds off of the work of Matthew Shugart, John Carey, Rein Taagepera, and others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>